Guide to the Charles Henry Pace and Frankie M. Pace Gospel Music Collection CAM.PAC.1999.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Printed Music, 1933-1951; III.
  - "Jericho," 50 Copies of Pages 3-6, 18.
  - "Jericho," 50 Copies of Pages 3-6, 19.
  - "Jericho," 50 Copies of Pages 3-6, 20.
  - "Jericho," 50 Copies of Pages 3-6, 21.
  - "Jericho," 50 Copies of Pages 3-6, 22.
  - "Jericho," 59 Copies of Pages 3-6, 23.
  - "Meet Me Where There'll Be No More Good-By," 19 Copies, 1945; 24.
  - "Meet Me Where There'll Be No More Good-By," 1 Heavily Soiled Copy, 1945; 25.
  - "Roll Memories Roll," 208 Copies, 1947; 26-39.
  - "Roll Memories Roll," 86 Copies of Page 3-4, 1947; 40-43.
  - "Something That's New", 44.
  - Other Gospel Songwriter's Printed Music, 1933-1951
    This section contains music from ten different songwriters. Most likely this collection also includes published works by other gospel songwriters because the Old Ship of Zion Music Company served as a distributing house for such works and/or bought out other publishing companies.
    - Professor E.C. Davis, Let Your Hearts Catch on Fire, 36 Copies of Page 2, 1934; 45.
    - Thomas A. Dorsey, I Got Heaven in My View, 1 Copy of Page 2, 1933; 46.
    - Thomas A. Dorsey, Lead Me to the Rock That's Higher than I, 1951, 1 Copy of Page 2, 47.
    - Thomas A. Dorsey, When I Can Read My Title Clear, 3 Copies, 48.
    - Thomas A. Dorsey, Wings Over Jordan!, 1 Copy, 1939; 49.
    - Thomas A. and Thomas M. Dorsey, I Got Jesus in My Soul, 1 Copy, 1945; 50.
    - Anne C. Graham, Don't Wonder About Him, 2 Copies, 1944; 51.
    - Chas. H. Hansen Music Company, Standin' In the Need of Prayer; Heav'n, Heav'n, 1 Copy, 1946; 52.
    - Emma L. Jackson, Have You Decided Which Way Your Soul Will Go? 1 Copy, 1943; 53.
    - Roberta Martin, The Angles Are Hovering 'Round, 1 Copy, 1944; 54.
    - Roberta Martin, It is Well, It is Well with My Soul, 1 Copy, 1944; 55.
    - Roberta Martin, My Lord is Writing all the Time, 1 Copy, 1942; 56.
    - Kenneth Morris, I am Walking With My Jesus, 6 Copies, 1943; 57.
    - Kenneth Morris, I'm Trying to Make Heaven My Home, 1 Copy of Page 2, 1943; 58.
    - Kenneth Morris, Till We Meet Again, 1944, 3 Copies, 59.
    - Lillian Morrow, I've had a Hard Time Seeking for My Lord, 3 Copies of Page 2, 1944; 60.
    - Mary Thames, You Just Keep in Touch with the Lord, 9 Copies, 1944; 61.
    - A. B. Windom, There's Rest for the Weary, 14 Copies, 1945; 62.
- Miscellaneous, 1822-1958; IV.
  The contents in the miscellaneous collection are items that are not a significant part of the collection. The files are arranged alphabetically.
  - Excerpt from Dictionary of Afro-American Performers Concerning Pace Jubilee Singers, 1.
  - Handwritten Note with Lyrics, 2.
  - Note Paper with Names and Addresses, 3.
  - Pages 2 and 3 of The Music of Charles Henry Pace, 4.
  - Photocopy (half) of Facts About the Negro Maudelle, 5.
  - Photocopy of the cover of Negro Plot and Account of the Late Intended Insurrection Among A Portion of the Blacks of the City of Charleston, South Carolina, 1822; 6.
  - Postcard Requesting Divine Love, 1957; 7.
  - Twenty Envelopes with Return Address of "Old Ship of Zion", 1943, 1945-1947; 8.
  - Sherman's Store Postcard Addressed to Mrs. Charles Pace, 1957; 9.
  - Various Photocopied Ads for Columbia, Okeh, and Paramount Records, 10.
  - Miscellaneous - General, 1958, Other Dates Unknown; 11.